

09231949790

justinecarcedo123@gmail.com

• Looc, Malabuyoc, Cebu

EXPERTISE

- Fast learner
- can troubleshoot problems regarding electronic components
- knows electronic components and it's parts
- can adapt to some work environments
- have a little knowledge aboutprogramming

LANGUAGE

English

Tagalog

Cebuano

CARCEDO JUSTIN

Electronic technician

ABOUT ME

I am an expert at hardware engineering and software engineering, I can analyze, compute and design electronic devices. that is for hardware engineering, for software engineering I use different kinds of programming languages such as java, html, python, C++ and C#.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Bachelor of Industrial Technology Major in Computer Engineering

Cebu Technological University
Ginatilan Extension Campus

2023 - present

TVL - EIM

Montañeza National High

2019 - 2023

School

Looc Integrated School

2011 - 2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

Panasonic
2019 - 2020
Electronic technician
I helped manufacturing some electronics such as fridges, Air
conditioning units, and microwaves

Nvidia
2012 - 2015
Electronic engineer
i helped analyze the requirements and costs of
electrical systems. I have also designed some gpu
and CPU components compatible for computers.

REFERENCES

Sheramae Cadungog - PC instructor +639548327303

John Joseph Sta. Ana - 09366209041

Ronvi Glend Roda -Ronvi12355@gmail.com